Kevin Gerstner



sirkevinicus@gmail.com



314-614-2301

Work Experience

Graphic Design Intern @ ArchCity Defenders

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019 \\ SAINT LOUIS, MO

- » Made digital art recreation of clients using Photoshop for print and web marketing
- » Created social media graphics, one of which got over 300 shares on Facebook
- » Researched social justice issues and communicated key issues to the affected communities

Research Assistant @ University of Tulsa

OCT 2018 - APR 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Researched, co-authored and published a paper with Prof. Sandeep Kuttal entitled: "Remote Pair-Programming in Online CS Education: Investigating through a Gender Lens", which was presented in the 2019 VL/HCC (Visual Languages & Human Centric Computing) conference.

Game Navigator & Server @ Shuffles Board Game Café SEP 2018 - JAN 2019 \\ TULSA, OK

Taught parties of people how to play board games, as well as taking orders and delivering food. In my spare time, I read rule books to learn new games.

Projects

Portfolio Website kevingerstner.com Web Developer \\ 2021

- Designed and coded a portfolio website using HTML, CSS/SASS, Bootstrap 5, and JS
- » Used Netlify to host and Namecheap for domain
- » Worked with web-friendly standards like Responsive Design, WEBM/P files, and Lighthouse

Tomb of Khaibit BLU3 J3LL0 Studios

Environment Designer & Tools Programmer $\setminus \setminus$ 2021

- » Created a Unity editor tool called Texo that can make procedurally generated dungeons
- » Made pixel art for the tomb environment using Aseprite

Song Pong NULLVALU_Studios

Feature Developer & Artist \\ 2020

- » Made a rhythm game inspired by the 80s and Pong in three months with the Unity engine
- » Coded features like spawning notes along to the beat and a song editor
- » Created art assets in Illustrator and Blender

Knock-Out! Global Smackdown Board Game Interactive Jeans Board Game Designer & Artist \\ 2018

- » Created over 150 unique card artworks, box art, and graphics for marketing
- » Created a Wordpress website
- » Launched a Kickstarter campaign

Summary

Passionate, well-rounded developer and designer with experience creating C# games in Unity and websites with HTML, SASS, and JS. Will graduate in 2021 with BS Computer Science / Art & Math Minor. Excellent at working with a team to implement ideas to create a finished product. Picks up new skills quickly.

Skills

Programming Languages

C# • Java • C++ • HTML • CSS/ SASS • jQuery • JavaScript

Tools & Platforms

Unity • Visual Studio • GitHub • ClickUp • Eclipse • Netlify • Word-Press • itch.io

Design

Photoshop • Illustrator • InDesign • Figma • Aseprite

Education

University of Tulsa 2017 - 2021 \\ TULSA, OK

B.S. in Computer Science and B.S. in Computer Simulation and Gaming with Math and Art minors

Interests

Board Games, Overwatch, Art, Animated movies, Horror Games, Music, Coffee